Israel awards gas exploration licenses to ENI, BP, and four others.
October 30th, Jerusalem, Israel's energy ministry said on Sunday it had awarded 12 licenses to six companies to explore for natural gas off the country's Mediterranean coast, aiming to create more competition and diversify suppliers.
The license awards, which came as the Israel-Hamas conflict entered its fourth week, included Italy's ENI along with Dana Petroleum and Israel's Ratio Energies.
This is Gaza. This is the Mediterranean Sea.
March 2023, Israel and Italy to increase cooperation in number of fields, Maloney pledges. Maloney is Italy's far-right prime minister.
So what we've put together here is that in March, Israel met with the far-right prime minister of Italy, Maloney.
They made a deal to be cooperating and now here we are in October and on October 30th, Italy was provided with a contract to search for natural gas off the coast of Gaza, which is being currently invaded by Israel.
So there's a couple of things that we learned from this.
One, we learned that this is why we read the news.
This is why we expand our parameters of information because it allows us to see things in a macro versus a micro.
And that macro is how we're able to determine where we put our support, where we put our money, where we put our hearts, where we put our people.
Two, we learned that unfortunately what we're witnessing is what many of us intrinsically have always known since this conflict began, that it was ultimately about money, land, and resources.
And that Jewish lives and Palestinian lives have been lost for the sake of advancing the power of few.
This is the result of settler colonialism.
It is always the pursuance of someone else's resources at the behest of their violence against them.
And when it comes to white supremacy, that has always been a accompanying proponent.
It is imperative that we point these things out because it lets us understand what we really should be fighting for.
And it helps us understand who the actual enemy is and how we are being so often led astray.
You know, one thing about white supremacy is that it chooses who gets to benefit from it.
And you don't have to be considered white to benefit from white supremacy.
They just have to decide that you are the next benefactor and it has to benefit them.
And from my studies, what I've deduced is that the number one way that white supremacy manifests is it's a parasite.
So it just finds another host.
Okay?
And once it finds that host, it's kind of like those fungus parasites that can get into the mind of an insect and control it.
You know, it's kind of like the Cruciatus Curse in Hogwarts.
And ultimately, in Harry Potter.
And ultimately, what happens is that it finds a host and it now controls that host.
And it convinces that host that it has an enemy.
And that in order for that host to stay alive, that host must then feed on an enemy.
That is what white supremacy does.
Because it convinces people that in order for them to exist, someone else has to not exist.
As a black person in America, we have watched white people believe this lie as they spit on Ruby Bridges as she walked into a classroom her first day of school.
We see it in the efforts to create access to white supremacy by Italians and Irish people in America so that they could now be the class that was tasked with keeping black people in place.
That's why there's so many Irish cops.
And we see it now.